Let me just keep this real simple for y'all. Anybody that supports genocide and is not loudly denouncing it is not getting my vote, is not getting my endorsement, is not getting my support.
Anybody that takes corporate money is not getting my vote, is not getting my endorsement, is not getting my support.
The fact that so many of you all do not see those things as non-starters is what actually reveals you to be un-intellectual voters, uninformed voters, and low vibrational people.
And that's what you don't want to hear. You don't want to hear that your values are in the gutter.
You don't want to hear that genocide is not a red line for you because you're so selfish that you only care about what can be done for yourself.
You don't want to hear that you don't know s*** about politics. You actually don't know anything about the way the government works.
You just like that it's somebody that you like. And that is actually what has continuously kept all of us in the gutter here in this nation.
But you don't want to hear that. You want to feel like I'm talking out my a**s. You want to feel like I'm annoying.
You want to feel like I'm all these things. And I'm none of those things.
I'm a high-character, high-quality individual. And all of us who are the same high-quality, high-character people feel the same about low-quality politics.
And that is all the United States actually engages in. Wake up!
The United States has an unbreakable bond with Israel.
Israel is a true friend. It is our greatest ally in the region.
The International Criminal Court singles out Israel, but not Iran.
It's great to be here at the annual conference in support of the U.S.-Israel relationship.
A relationship that, of course, is anchored in our shared values.
Always also made clear that we continue to support Israel's right to defend itself.